<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<title>The Truth About Santa</title>
	<subtitle>Learn the sinister truth behind Santa today.</subtitle>
	<link href="/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
	<link href=""/>
	<updated>2021-11-22T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
	<id></id>
	<author>
		<name>The Santa Truthers</name>
	</author>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Santa&#39;s Connection to the spread of Coronavirus began on Christmas Eve</title>
		<link href="/2020/06/02/santas-connection-to-the-spread-of-coronavirus-began-on-christmas-eve/"/>
		<updated>2020-06-02T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
		<id>/2020/06/02/santas-connection-to-the-spread-of-coronavirus-began-on-christmas-eve/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Coronavirus mysteriously appeared after Christmas. While it was not until March that government officials started enforcing quarantine and other measures, supposed Flu patients who died in early January tested positive for Covid-19. Obviously, Coronavirus could not have been brought to the United States and Europe by Chinese travelers—Coronavirus was in the United States BEFORE there was a severe outbreak in China!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to the International Date Line and Time Zones, Santa clause, when planned strategically, receives a full 24 hours to distribute presents. This journey would start at the International Date Line, heading west. China and North Korea would be prime locations to start.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Santa collects many of his goods from Chinese factories and travels up through Siberia to the North Pole on Christmas Eve. Santa must bring his reindeer into Northern North Korea to successfully launch his sleigh to deliver presents in time. THE ONLY WAY TO DELAY SANTA IS TO STRENGTHEN OUR MILITARY!! North Korea welcomes Santa’s sleigh because it will soon allow them to gain more power.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are the indisputable &lt;strong&gt;facts&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Santa and his communist cohorts created the &lt;em&gt;terrible&lt;/em&gt; &lt;strong style=&quot;color:red&quot;&gt;coronavirus&lt;/strong&gt; to make people &amp;quot;well-behaved&amp;quot; Santa-believing communists. Using Santa&#39;s technology, the Communists collaborated to transmit Coronavirus FROM THE TOYS TO THE CHILDREN! The children would pass it to the Parents and Grandparents and so on!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kim Jong-Un is chubby like Santa! Could he actually be Santa? Beware! Could it be that? Coronavirus was the “gift” Kim Jong-Un promised President Trump last year? It doesn&#39;t seem impossible! Santa and his evil helpers were planning this all along.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Santa’s Plan worked perfectly. Now, the GREAT United States has well over one million cases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;But it’s much worse!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The North Poleans hoarded supplies from OUR SHELVES but experienced no cases! While China seemed to have a big problem, the problem was really staged to take more people to forced labor and other nasty lifestyles. North Korea and the North Pole have reported no cases at all! China’s cases have gone up none for a long while!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, Capitalism allowed thousands of people to begin making masks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But Santa is still hiding in the shadows!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a while, many experts could not explain China’s, North Korea’s, and the North Pole’s low numbers. HOWEVER, SANTATRUTH HAS FOUND THE TRUTH AFTER MUCH REASEARCH! The Coronavirus was planned! we know this by Kim Jong-Un warning President Trump of a “gift”! As noted above, Kim Jong-Un is Santa!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After creating the Coronavirus, Santa&#39;s Doctors also created a vaccination for the Reindeer, the Elves, and the workers. The Vaccination is completely secret with no way of finding the formula! But Communist Country’s workers are completely safe while our people die.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is only one way to stop this. We must tell our children that SANTA IS OUT TO GET THEM! They will refuse any toxic toys or any other forms of propaganda! Protect the future!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These are simple facts. You can make your own conclusion, but we must #StopSanta before it is too late! Make sure that you are not being brainwashed by Santa&#39;s propaganda yourself!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Join the movement to &lt;strong&gt;#StopSanta&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-covid.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Santa and Coronavirus&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-covid.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-covid-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-covid-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-covid-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-covid-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-covid-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Santa&#39;s Sinister Connection to the Coronavirus</title>
		<link href="/2020/06/02/santas-sinister-connection-to-the-coronavirus/"/>
		<updated>2020-06-02T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
		<id>/2020/06/02/santas-sinister-connection-to-the-coronavirus/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The facts:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Coronavirus supposedly came from China, a communist nation that is known to be one of Santa&#39;s top collaborators in mindwashing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Many of Santa&#39;s presents are made in China. Just check the labels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa is known as the world&#39;s greatest philanthropist. Could he be a co-conspirator of George Soros and Bill Gates?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/apr/10/larry-hogan-maryland-governor-declares-easter-bunn/&quot;&gt;Governor Larry Hogan declared Santa&#39;s close associate, the &lt;span style=&quot;color:red&quot;&gt;The Eater Bunny&lt;/span&gt;, an essential worker. Was this just to further the mind-controlling effects of Santa?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is it any coincidence that the virus emerged immediately after Christmas?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-covid.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Santa and Coronavirus&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-covid.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-covid-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-covid-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-covid-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-covid-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-covid-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Exclusive interview: 5G and Santa investigation interview with John Grellysh</title>
		<link href="/2020/08/03/exclusive-interview-5g-and-santa-investigation-interview/"/>
		<updated>2020-08-03T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
		<id>/2020/08/03/exclusive-interview-5g-and-santa-investigation-interview/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;SantaTruth asked John Grellysh and his team to investigate Santa&#39;s connection to 5G. His findings were astounding. SantaTruth&#39;s Lizzy Edith interviews John Grellysh on the details of the investigation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lizzy Edith: Thank you for being here with us today John!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John Grellysh: Yeah, thank you for having me!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: SantaTruth members are wondering about Santa&#39;s hand with 5G. We&#39;ve heard a lot about 5G and Santa, so did Santa &lt;em&gt;create&lt;/em&gt; 5G?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: No, Santa actually didn&#39;t create 5G. Basically what happened is there were a bunch of Chineese people who wanted collect more data from Americans. Anyway, the technology was new, and it wasn&#39;t really safe. But China, of course, doesn&#39;t care about saftey. Basically, they stole the technology and started manufacturing. Now, Santa comes in. Santa saw an opportunity to watch people better. He had been collaborating with the Chineese already on Covid-19. This was about a decade ago. At the time, Covid-19 really didn&#39;t have any way to spread, so Santa suggested to make Covid-19 spew out of 5G. Anyway, China really didn&#39;t have the labor fource for the 5G manufacturing. Santa really couldn&#39;t manufacture it in the Norh Pole, but while the Chineese continued to produce other goods, Santa took the reins and started producing 5G towers. We looked at one and found that actually Covid-19 was supposed to start spewing out on December 25, right after Santa left back to the North Pole. 5G continues to be put in place. It&#39;s really a project from the North Pole for many purposes, but Santa didn&#39;t start it, he took it over.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: So was it initially just for spreading Coronavirus?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: I don&#39;t know. It&#39;s hard to tell when the events happened. We know that Santa started working on Covid-19 approximatly in 2009 or so; we don&#39;t have an exact number. But we&#39;re pretty sure that Santa picked up 5G manufacturing for multiple reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: What are some other reasons then?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: The big four we found were spreading Covid-19, propaganda on phones and computers, mass surveillance, and messing with people&#39;s brains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: What exactly do you mean by messing with people&#39;s brains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: Oh, well, of course Covid-19, propaganda, and mass surveillance messes with your brain, but I&#39;m refering to the energy interfearing with your brain cell function. What we found was there were actually controls that allowed Santa and the Chineese to change the signals to mess with people&#39;s brains differently. Right now, it&#39;s basically making people believe Communism is the answer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: Right, we&#39;re seeing that right now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: Yeah, you do have a lot of people who are now thinking that Communism might work, even though China is responsible for Covid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: Huh, that&#39;s interesting. But are they just sending invisible propaganda into brains?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: No, not exactly. Basically, no intelligent mind believes Communism works. That&#39;s why they need propaganda. Basically, because there&#39;s all kinds sources on the internet pointing out the flaws in Communism--&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: Like SantaTruth--&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: Yup, like SantaTruth basically, the energy from the 5G waves destroys the brain to the point that they can&#39;t wrap their mind around the basic truth of the world. Then, using mass surveillance, they will send all kinds of propaganda to us. And we&#39;re already seeing the results of this like in Portland. In other words, they&#39;re using the destructive 5G waves to make us believe their propaganda.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: And what kind of propaganda?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: It&#39;s hard to say. There&#39;s two types. The first is normal, Communist propaganda, which we havn&#39;t seen too much of yet because people havn&#39;t been brainwashed all the way. Second, is advertisments. You see a lot of stuff from China being advertised more, even though it&#39;s cheaper. Really, it&#39;s junk that breaks so we keep buying more and more. Keep in mind, China has already mastered our minds, and it&#39;s because of Santa&#39;s connection to small children why they understand it. Basically, they hope to make enough money off of plastic junk to build up the resources to take over the world. And they&#39;ve already made a lot of money. 5G may completely get them enough money to succeed. That alone should make us want to push back on 5G.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: But they&#39;re using that for other purposes too. &lt;em&gt;All&lt;/em&gt; of them alone should want to make us to push back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: Right, right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: What about the mass surveillance part?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: Well, Santa has already figured out mass surveillance, as we know, his infamous Naughty and Nice list. 5G allows Santa to collect all kinds of data. Basically, everything that you view, and everything that goes to you, and everything you send goes right through those towers, which goes right back to the North Pole. Before, Santa&#39;s surveillance was pretty much tied to those who chose accept Santa. But now it&#39;s reached a whole new level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: Wow. And he&#39;s using this data to track us in order to functionally take over the world?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: Yes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: Wow. That&#39;s terrifying. Now that we&#39;ve terrified our audience [laughs]--&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: I wouldn&#39;t say terrified, just informed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: Yeah. [laughs] It is, nevertheless terrifying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: It certainly is. But you don&#39;t have to be terrified.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: That&#39;s what I was going to get into. So what can we do to prevent it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: There&#39;s a lot of things you can do, starting with makeing your home safer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: And how&#39;s that done?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: The big one is making your walls safe. Basically, behind the drywall is studs, in between the studs is insulation. But behind the insulation is the outside wall. Anyway, cover the outside wall with tinfoil, and then cover it up with insulation and drywall. That&#39;s if you&#39;re building. Right now, SantaTruth is developing a reflective paint to paint on your walls if the drywall is already over it. Even with the reflective paint done, it&#39;s still a good idea if your building to put the tinfoil inside the walls. Buy some heavy curtains with a metalic compound, pull those over the windows at night. Also, quilts have layers, so it&#39;s a good idea to insirt a couple layers of tinfoil inbetween the layers of a quilt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: And what about when we&#39;re out of the house.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: Get a windbreaker, it can be a cheap one, but it has layers too. Cut it open and stick tinfoil in between the layers. Wear that wherever you go. You can also do that with a winter coat just so you don&#39;t have to wear too many coats when it&#39;s cold. Lining your shoes is a good idea, but not necessary, so is lining your underpants. One really important one is to get a hat, like a beanie or something, and line the inside of that with tinfoil. Wear that everywhere. It&#39;s a good idea to wear it at night unless you sleep with your head under the covers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: And what about devices?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: Disconnect it from the internet whenever possible, basically when you are not using it. It&#39;s also good to make a tinfoil sleeve for your devices. At night, shut them down, and put them in the tinfoil sleeve.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: Some folks use their phones as alarms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: Yeah, buy a battery-powered alarm! In general, if there is something that can be done without an internet connected device, use that alternative. That&#39;s a flashlight, calendar, you get the picture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: And Coronavirus, what about that?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: While Covid is a problem, most maks have a double layer. Poke a few holes in the tin foil for air flow, and insirt that between the layers of the mask. That makes sure that the 5G radiation doesn&#39;t get into your mouth and cause Covid in there. Wearing glases, and they can be sunglasses or even fake glasses, can help too. No tin foil there, of course as you could not see. But just having that extra layer helps prevent the waves from entering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: Anything else you&#39;d like to tell us?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: No, not really, just take SantaTruth&#39;s cautions seriously. They made a list on the website if I&#39;m correct?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: Yes, correct.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: OK, good. Just follow those guildlines; it could save your life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: And prevent Santa, who is really a problem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: Exactly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: Well, thank you for being here!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: Thanks for having me!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: And thank you for your work with 5G. It&#39;s really appreciated by all of us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: Yeah, absolutly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LE: Again, thank you, and we hope to get more information about 5G and Santa soon!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JG: You bet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-5g-interview.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Santa and 5G&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-5g-interview.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-5g-interview-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-5g-interview-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-5g-interview-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-5g-interview-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-5g-interview-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Investigation: Santa&#39;s Mysterious 5G Connection</title>
		<link href="/2020/08/03/investigation-santas-mysterious-5g-connection/"/>
		<updated>2020-08-03T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
		<id>/2020/08/03/investigation-santas-mysterious-5g-connection/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Santa is at it again! Now using 5G Cell Towers to BRAINWASH us. The electricity from these cell towers has been deemed highly dangerous by many, but SantaTruth&#39;s investigation revealed more terrible details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5G is made in China. Santa also has a connection to China. Santa has had a major hand in the production of 5G, and he wants it perfect...for him.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our team of investigators, lead by John Grellysh, dug into 5G&#39;s problems with an investigation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The facts from our investigation:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The energy from the 5G towers flows into your body and messes with your brain.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recently, a 5G tower was put up and Coronavirus broke out close by shortly after.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa created and has spread the Coronavirus in efforts to take over the world.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5G is just part of Santa&#39;s plan.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa recently started giving out phones to youngsters at Christmas in efforts to brainwash their minds! (As seen in a little known clipping below!)&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-pravda.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Pravda and Santa&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-pravda.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-pravda-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-pravda-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-pravda-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-pravda-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-pravda-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa is using 5G towers to connect new propaganda and data to phones!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The energy in the 5G waves flows through the body and destroys the mind.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eventually, the 5G waves will &lt;em&gt;convince&lt;/em&gt; people&#39;s minds that Communism is the answer and Santa is a great hero.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fourthly, Santa is using 5G for mass surveillance, to see who is &amp;quot;naughty&amp;quot; and who is &amp;quot;nice&amp;quot;, and, of course, we all know what that means when it comes to Communists.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recap&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa is using 5G to spread Coronavirus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa is using 5G to add new propaganda to phones and other devices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa is using 5G waves to mess with people&#39;s brains.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa is using 5G for mass surveillance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Santa is using 5G for his EVIL PLOY TO TAKE OVER THE WORLD!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our team of investigators also put together a full list of how you can prevent 5G and #StopSanta:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Insirt a layer of tinfoil inbetween the layers of a windbreaker and wear the windbreaker wherever you go and at night.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Find a hat that fits snugly around your head, line the inside with tinfoil, and wear wherever you go.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wear real, sun, or dummy (with plain glass) glasses everywhere to prevent waves from reaching your eyes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Insirt a layer of tinfoil into a quilt so you will be completely covered at night.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Layer your outside walls on the inside with tinfoil and then with drywall to prevent radiation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Buy heavy curtains with a metalic compound for your windows and close the curtains at night.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make sure to insirt a layer of tinfoil inbetween the layers of your mask while Coronavirus is a risk!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep your phone disconnected and buy limited data plans to prevent mass surveillance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create a tinfoil case for your phone whenever the phone is not in use. Shut down your phone at night and put it into the tinfoil case. Do likewise with all of your other devices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Buy a battery-powered alarm clock instead of using a phone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use a print calendar to schedule events and notepads to write down tasks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Install a landline phone and use instead of a cellphone whenever possible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Order news magazines and newspapers instead of using a phone or other device for news.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don&#39;t give your children any type of electronic device until they realize Santa is real and out to get them! Even if they can repeat so, still take great caution. Many are easily brainwashed. We recommend no electronic devices until age 14 at least.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use an ad blocking extention.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Disconnect from the internet whenever you are not using it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Beware of what you see online! Reference back to SantaTruth for the TRUTH!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take these cautions seriously. They could save your life.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#StopSanta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-5g.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Santa and 5G&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-5g.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-5g-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-5g-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-5g-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-5g-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-5g-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Santa, 5g, and the Apocalypse</title>
		<link href="/2020/08/03/santa-5g-and-the-apocalypse/"/>
		<updated>2020-08-03T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
		<id>/2020/08/03/santa-5g-and-the-apocalypse/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The facts:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5g is made by China, a communist nation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa is a communist&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;People have been concerned about 5g being used for spying, and even mind control&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa &amp;quot;sees you when you&#39;re sleeping&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;knows when your awake&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa often gives fancy new 5g-equipped phones as &amp;quot;gifts&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Could 5g be yet another evil Santa plot?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some people have said that 5g could be used by the coming Antichrist to assert control over the world.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Could Santa be collaborating with the Antichrist?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Could the &amp;quot;Mark of the Beast&amp;quot; be a Santa hat that everybody will be required to wear?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Could the woman on the cow be a metaphor for Santa&#39;s sleigh being pulled by reindeer?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-apocalypse.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Santa and the Apocalypse&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-apocalypse.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-apocalypse-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-apocalypse-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-apocalypse-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-apocalypse-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-apocalypse-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Santa&#39;s Sinister Connection to Mail-In Voting</title>
		<link href="/2020/08/03/santas-sinister-connection-to-mail-in-voting/"/>
		<updated>2020-08-03T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
		<id>/2020/08/03/santas-sinister-connection-to-mail-in-voting/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The facts:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;President Trump and many others have brought up concerns about Mail-In Voting Fraud.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa and his Chineese Comrades are looking to gain influence throughout the world with Coronavirus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa and China want neither Trump nor Biden to win, but will be using the fill-in option to elect a Santa-approved Communist with mail-in ballot fraud!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa and China have used Coronavirus as a ploy to take over the world. This is just one part of their deadly plan!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Call your representatives today and tell them Santa&#39;s sinister connection and his ploy to DESTROY!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make plans to vote in person. Stay socially distanced and wear a mask or Santa&#39;s Coronavirus will brainwash you and Santa will take over that way!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#StopSanta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-mail-box.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Santa and Coronavirus&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-mail-box.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-mail-box-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-mail-box-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-mail-box-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-mail-box-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-mail-box-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Why Santa faked the moon landing</title>
		<link href="/2020/08/19/why-santa-faked-the-moon-landing/"/>
		<updated>2020-08-19T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
		<id>/2020/08/19/why-santa-faked-the-moon-landing/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The facts:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Soviets were ahead in the Space Race, but suddenly their technology ran out. Was Santa supplying their technology? Did he stop supplying technology so he could do it through his own means?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The United States never had the technology to land on the moon. In a fashion similar to the the Soviets, the United States could not develop technology. If they had, the Soviets would have beat the US.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The only party that has technology advanced enough to reach outer space is Santa. He developed it with his sleigh. Santa&#39;s sleigh is from the Space Race.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Why did Santa fund the Soviets and then push the US to the moon? Perhaps it was to make Americans think that they were more powerful then they really were, while Santa had a large grip over the US! If we get too full of ourselves, it will put us in a vulnerable position--perfect for Santa!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa received millions of dollars for staging the moon landing from the Soviets and China.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Did Santa hack the computers to feed in staged footage? He probably either influenced the brains of the astronauts or threatened them to say they really landed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa is the only person (and the North Pole is the only country) that has enough technology to fly satelites, fly rockets, and reach space in general. Any type of  space exploration is faked by Santa to strengthen his grip. He is the only one with a flying sled!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rather than revealing himself, Santa continues to let NASA send rockets up. Why? Because huge amounts of top-seceret government information is sent &amp;quot;secretly&amp;quot; into space, and is being picked up by Santa for his benefits!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;China continues to pay Santa for US Government data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#StopSanta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-moon.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Santa and his riches from the moon landing&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-moon.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-moon-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-moon-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-moon-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-moon-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-moon-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Santa&#39;s Brainwashing Techniques: What to look out for</title>
		<link href="/2020/08/20/santas-brainwashing-techniques-what-to-look-out-for/"/>
		<updated>2020-08-20T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
		<id>/2020/08/20/santas-brainwashing-techniques-what-to-look-out-for/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Set aside Coronavirus. The world is a big mess. Is there an end to Coronavirus? &lt;em&gt;And&lt;/em&gt; everything else? 🤔 Anyone? This will make you think.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Santa is well known for Brainwashing. But his techniques are nearly invisible. You need to say informed on what to look out for!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently, there is a huge amount of conspiracy theories floating around. People will instead say that there are &amp;quot;alternate facts&amp;quot; when they want to ignore the truth! Nobody knows the truth. The truth is that Santa is pushing these theories to brainwash us! It is a Communist project to see how gullible the civilized western world is! Are these theories created by Santa to try to devide us and make us so afraid that Santa can take over?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Santa is making us scared. Scared of the virus? Scared of masks? Scared of people? Scared of no people? Scared of the government? Scared of no police? These fears are created by Santa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When will Coronavirus go away? Will it resurge? Why is everything so uncertian?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is Santa trying to make us afraid of the doctor&#39;s advice so that he can brainwash us when we get Coronavirus?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone has an opinion on everything...except for why people are scared. Is this another ploy of Santa? Nobody brings up Santa...and Santa likes it that way! Do we unconsciously and unknowingly know that Santa will quash us if we tell the truth? Is Santa shading the truth? Or making us disbelieve Santa&#39;s sinister hand in everthing? (At least this post is already up! Try to get me now Santa!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We know Santa is trying to disrupt the United States election this year. Is he trying to devide us worse and create a Communist state?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And all of the technology our children will be using in school will be made in China. Is Santa trying to brainwash our children by growing internet usage? After all, the internet is one of many of Santa&#39;s brainwashing projects! Could Coronavirus just be an extended project? Or could anti-Coronavirus theories be part of an extended project? Be careful what your children are using the internet for!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are Russia and China paying Santa to spread these theories? After all, China and Russia are Santa&#39;s biggest sponsors. Seeing their Communist ties and their goals to take over the world, wouldn&#39;t it be logical for them to be helping Santa in this project? Santa is already selling these countries huge amounts of data from our internet AND from government satellites!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We know that Santa has taken big actions to try to brainwash our children using technology. (As seen in a little-known issue of Pravda, shared only by SantaTruth!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-pravda.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Pravda and Santa&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-pravda.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-pravda-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-pravda-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-pravda-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-pravda-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-pravda-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is Santa using Coronavirus theories to spread uncertainty and division to weaken the United States so he can finally take it over?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why are we so nervous about this? Even the people who &lt;em&gt;don&#39;t&lt;/em&gt; believe in Coronavirus are nervous!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is this all just a final ending? Or is it a beginning of Santa&#39;s regime?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s hard to tell these days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How can you know what is Communist or not? Or, for that matter, true or not? &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wouldn&#39;t it be logical to only believe the only anti-Santa organization, SantaTruth?&lt;/strong&gt; And believe nothing else?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#StopSanta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-children-propaganda.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Santa Brainwashing poor helpless children&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-children-propaganda.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-children-propaganda-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-children-propaganda-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-children-propaganda-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-children-propaganda-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-children-propaganda-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Does Santa control Facebook?</title>
		<link href="/2020/08/22/does-santa-control-facebook/"/>
		<updated>2020-08-22T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
		<id>/2020/08/22/does-santa-control-facebook/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The facts:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facebook is well known for it&#39;s tracking. Just read their privacy policy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant ads that are targeted at you come up all the time on Facebook. Are these propaganda ads from Santa?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We know Santa loves brainwashing and stealing YOUR PERSONAL DATA! Wouldn&#39;t Facebook be a logical place to pick up his data?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is Facebook yet another propaganda machine controled by Santa?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa and the North Pole, a major technology deveoloper, has stayed hidden from Social Media. Or has he?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is it any coincidence that Facebook is bias in favor of Marxist theology?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#StopSanta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-facebook.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Santa and Facebook&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-facebook.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-facebook-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-facebook-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-facebook-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-facebook-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-facebook-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Is Santa hacking Twitter?</title>
		<link href="/2020/08/22/is-santa-hacking-twitter/"/>
		<updated>2020-08-22T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
		<id>/2020/08/22/is-santa-hacking-twitter/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The facts:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recently, there have been Twitter hacks trying to get money and brainwash people. Could this be the work of Santa?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa has used many methods to brainwash us with Coronavirus. Is he trying to get even more money by hacking Twitter?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Steve Schmidt recently attacked Sen. Marco Rubio trying to tie him to the Communists in Cuba. Could Santa be making Rubio&#39;s supporters believe that Rubio is a Communist?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rubio supposedly responded saying that Schmidt was part of a party that was Marxist. Was Santa trying to make Democrats believe in Marxism?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How can supporters of either side know if Communism is right or wrong? Is it assumed that it&#39;s bad? Or will supporters think it&#39;s fine? Did Rubio and Schmidt ACTUALLY write these Tweets?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-twitter-hack-one.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Marco Rubio and Steve Schmidt frame each other as Communists on Twitter&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-twitter-hack-one.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-twitter-hack-one-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-twitter-hack-one-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-twitter-hack-one-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-twitter-hack-one-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-twitter-hack-one-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The accounts Bill Gates, Former President Barack Obama, Former Vice-President Joe Biden, Elon Musck, Apple, Kanye West, and more were hacked with information where to send Bitcoin. The scam was thankfully quickly spotted. But how much did Santa make from the short time?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SantaTruth blocked out the address for the saftey of our readers, but it is clear that the adress is a scam, clearly Santa&#39;s address!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-twitter-hack-two.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Bill Gates&#39;s account hacked with information on where to send Bitcoin&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-twitter-hack-two.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-twitter-hack-two-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-twitter-hack-two-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-twitter-hack-two-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-twitter-hack-two-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-twitter-hack-two-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Former President Barack Obama said he was giving back due to Covid-19. Was Santa trying to make even more money off the virus he created?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-twitter-hack-three.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Barack Obama&#39;s account hacked asking peple to send Bitcoin&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-twitter-hack-three.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-twitter-hack-three-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-twitter-hack-three-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-twitter-hack-three-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-twitter-hack-three-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-twitter-hack-three-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is it any coincidence that Santa is trying to gain more money from a virus he created?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-twitter.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Santa and Coronavirus&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-twitter.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-twitter-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-twitter-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-twitter-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-twitter-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-twitter-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Santa&#39;s Sinister Coronavirus Brainwashing Techniques</title>
		<link href="/2020/08/22/santas-sinister-coronavirus-brainwashing-techniques/"/>
		<updated>2020-08-22T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
		<id>/2020/08/22/santas-sinister-coronavirus-brainwashing-techniques/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Santa is using Coronavirus to brainwash YOU and YOUR FAMILY! From sending 5G waves to spread Coronavirus and cause brain manipulation, to the phsycological dissorders from Coronavirus, you need to know the facts about Santa&#39;s sinister connection to Coronavirus brain manipulation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The facts:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Coronavirus supposedly came from China, a communist nation that is known to be one of Santa&#39;s top collaborators in mindwashing. Could it be that Santa and the Chineese created the virus and launched it in China?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;China didn&#39;t reveal their Coronavirus problems to the rest of the world until it was too late. Was this part of Santa&#39;s ploy?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are seeing 5G cause Coronavirus. 5G is made in China. Santa is the only one who has the power to make 5G. And more people are using 5G because the world has gone online!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do you have friends who have had Coronavirus? Do you notice them being more Marxist and pro-Santa? Do you find them wishing for the &amp;quot;happiness&amp;quot; of Christmas (i.e. Santa breaking into your house and watching you)?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;China hoarded masks when Coronavirus started. SantaTruth showed that masks can prevent radio waves from entering your mouth and brainwashing you. What&#39;s next?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa is pushing for legislation that would force you to get vaccinated with the Coronavirus vaccine. Is this going to make you get Coronavirus? Are you going to be microchiped? Remember, microchip technology is made in China and developed by Santa. Santa has done most of the reasearch!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have you heard about Coronavirus cases in the North Pole? Did Santa figure out how to prevent them?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Soon after Coronavirus, protests emerged accros the United States and then the world. Did Santa brainwash people so they would be angry at eachother? Why wern&#39;t they protesting before? Why did the problems that they&#39;re protesting start after Coronavirus? Or is Santa trying to make them get Coronavirus by protesting? It&#39;s hard to tell.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa has been taking a large online presence including influencing social media trying to brainwash YOUR CHILDREN. Did Santa spread Coronavirus so that your children would be online and therefore slammed with Santa&#39;s propaganda?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Santa is brainwashing us with:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coronavirus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5G&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The internet&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microchips in the Coronavirus Vaccine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have you taken appropriate measures to protect your family?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/08/03/investigation-santas-mysterious-5g-connection&quot;&gt;(Get information about protecting your family from 5G here.)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prevent yourself from getting Coronavirus:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wear a mask and stay 6 feet (2 meters) apart.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoid going out at all costs!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you do need to go out, wear goggles to prevent Coronavirus from getting in your eyes--the worst!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make sure you&#39;re washing your hand with three squirts of soap and one minute with hot water. Don&#39;t touch door handles or anything else. Use hand sanitizer as necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stay home.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cover for sneezes and coughs well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hose down everything with lysol and whatnot to make sure none of Santa&#39;s germs survive!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you have symptoms, get a test. If you test positive, make sure you&#39;re subscribed to SantaTruth so you don&#39;t get BRAINWASHED!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoid using the Internet. Deleate your Facebook and TikTok account. They&#39;re dangerous!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep up-to-date on SantaTruth. The only reliable source during the pandemic!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We need to &lt;strong&gt;#StopSanta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-brainwash.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Santa and Coronavirus&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-brainwash.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-brainwash-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-brainwash-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-brainwash-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-brainwash-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-brainwash-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Why you should never let your children use TikTok!</title>
		<link href="/2020/08/22/why-you-sould-never-let-your-children-use-tiktok/"/>
		<updated>2020-08-22T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
		<id>/2020/08/22/why-you-sould-never-let-your-children-use-tiktok/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The facts:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;TikTok is a Chineese company that tracks you. It&#39;s been in the news because it was banned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;However, TikTok can be sold to a United States company. The danger still exists.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;While China may not be able to gather data to send to Santa from TikTok, TikTok&#39;s code shows that after a US company buys TikTok, data will still be sent to Santa. There is no way to stop this!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa loves selling data to China!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;TikTok&#39;s tracking policies show Santa all of your personal information on your device. It even tracks the names of other files when you upload a video and how you use the device!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do you want your children to be brainwashed by a Chineese propaganda project?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is there any evidence showing that TikTok will not be controled by Communists even if the Communists don&#39;t own it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We need to Wake Up! Santa will track your children and endoctrinate your children if you let them download TikTok!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&quot;color: red; font-family: chiller; font-size: 200%;&quot;&gt;UPDATE: TikTok has not been banned in the United States, showing just how COMMUNIST and CORRUPT the legal system is!!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/09/23/santa-on-the-supreme-court&quot;&gt;(Read more about Santa&#39;s legal system connections here.)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#StopSanta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-tiktok.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Santa and TikTok&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-tiktok.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-tiktok-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-tiktok-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-tiktok-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-tiktok-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-tiktok-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Santa on the Supreme Court?</title>
		<link href="/2020/09/23/santa-on-the-supreme-court/"/>
		<updated>2020-09-23T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
		<id>/2020/09/23/santa-on-the-supreme-court/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Santa is now trying to control the Supreme Court--the only United States branch of government where Santa can&#39;t hack the election! Knowing that it would be a long time before he could make the Supreme Court Communist, Santa is now trying to become the Supreme Court Justice to fill RBG&#39;s seat!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are the FACTS:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After RBG&#39;s death, Mitch McConnell promised to fill RBG&#39;s seat before the election.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Even before a nominee was named, Santa BRAINWASHED PEOPLE TO MAKE THEM NOT WANT TO FILL THE SEAT!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As we already know, Santa has hacked mail-in ballots to make a Communist win the presidential election. The next president who will fill RBG&#39;s seat will be a Communist!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With Santa or one of his comrads on the Supreme Court, the Supreme Court will become Communist because Santa is influencing the minds of the justices!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unless we hate freedom, we have to say NO to Santa on the Supreme Court.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#StopSanta&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-supreme-court.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Santa and Coronavirus&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-supreme-court.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-supreme-court-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-supreme-court-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-supreme-court-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-supreme-court-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-supreme-court-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>What to think of the election results</title>
		<link href="/2020/11/12/what-to-think-about-the-election-result/"/>
		<updated>2020-11-12T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
		<id>/2020/11/12/what-to-think-about-the-election-result/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;As predicted by SantaTruth, a Democrat-turned-Communist won the presidency. Here&#39;s what you need to know:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Joe Biden isn&#39;t bad but he will be influenced by Santa.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Joe Biden will think the job of president is easy because Santa will be doing it for him--without Biden knowing!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We should accept the election results because we need to prepare for the Communist regeme--not protest.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa will take over soon unless we raise awareness now!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&#39;s how you can prepare!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don&#39;t do anything that could be dangerous!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow all the guidelines that SantaTruth ever puts out, whatever they may be!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tell your friends so they can prepare too.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We need to take action NOW!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#StopSanta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/joe-biden.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Joe Biden&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/joe-biden.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/joe-biden-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/joe-biden-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/joe-biden-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/joe-biden-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/joe-biden-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Official Christmas Movie Ratings: We Watched Christmas Movies to Rate How Much They Promoted Communism</title>
		<link href="/2020/11/16/official-christmas-movie-ratings/"/>
		<updated>2020-11-16T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
		<id>/2020/11/16/official-christmas-movie-ratings/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;a-charlie-brown-christmas&quot;&gt;A Charlie Brown Christmas&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Charlie Brown Christmas does not portray Santa as a friendly comrade but fails to denounce Communism. In fact, characters complain about the commercialism of Christmas. At least the “true meaning of Christmas” does not conclude to be faith in Santa and Communism. Rating: 5/10&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&quot;miracle-on-34th-street&quot;&gt;Miracle on 34th Street&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Miracle on 34th Street is fine until Santa proves himself real. It is fine to show to your children but make sure to stop it just after Santa announces he has failed the insanity test. Do not watch to the end! The movie ends with Santa proving himself to truly be Santa, people begin to believe in Santa, and he makes their wishes come true. Rating: 2/10&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&quot;how-the-grinch-stole-christmas!&quot;&gt;How the Grinch Stole Christmas!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not terrible, but the movie portrays Santa as a kind character. Also, the Grinch fails to denounce Santa once his heart has been converted. Rating: 3/10&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&quot;rudolph-the-red-nosed-reindeer&quot;&gt;Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DO NOT WATCH! The Movie portrays Santa’s workshop in a favorable way, promoting the elves forceful toymaking activities. Some parts of the Communism do slip! There is a task driver who forces the elves about there business and one elf is fired after failing to achieve his assigned tasks. The poor elf could not even pursue the job he wanted! Rudolph is also rejected because of his red nose even though he is one of the finest reindeers. The movie, rather than showing Rudolph suing Santa, portrays Santa, Rudolph, and others being welcomed kindly back home before Rudolph assists Santa in brainwashing helpless children. This is a true example of Santa’s propaganda! Rating: 1/10&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&quot;frosty-the-snowman&quot;&gt;Frosty the Snowman&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While not promoting Santa at first, the children’s “magical” snowman puts a poor magician benefiting from capitalism out of a job and Santa eventually saves Frosty’s life. Rating: 1/10&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-year-without-a-santa-clause&quot;&gt;The Year Without a Santa Clause&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another dangerous film! The movie portrays Santa not wanting to go on his Christmas adventure. The elves try to prove that people still believe in Santa and eventually succeed. In conclusion, Santa decides to go on his journey because a little girl writes to him telling him how much she will miss him. This will make your children want to have Santa come! Rating: 1/10&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&quot;mr.-smith-goes-to-washington&quot;&gt;Mr. Smith Goes to Washington&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The only good film! While not a Christmas film, still a worthy watch. The only problem is Mr. Smith beats the fellow capitalists, not communists. Also, Mr. Smith never denounces communism and Santa. At the very least, this will not brainwash your children and will teach then about freedom! Rating: 8/10&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&quot;it%E2%80%99s-a-wonderful-life&quot;&gt;It’s a Wonderful Life&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not terrible. Two notes of caution: First, one of George Bailey’s sons wears a Santa hat. Second, the film never denounces Communism and, in mild ways, portrays those who benefit from capitalism in an unfavorable way. Fortunately, the hero benefits from capitalism too. It is fine to watch but be sure to have a conversation with your children about the horrors of Communism after. Rating: 6/10&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#StopSanta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-children-propaganda.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Official Santa Movie Ratings&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-children-propaganda.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-children-propaganda-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-children-propaganda-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-children-propaganda-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-children-propaganda-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-children-propaganda-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Is Santa a Freemason?</title>
		<link href="/2021/10/27/is-santa-a-freemason/"/>
		<updated>2021-10-27T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
		<id>/2021/10/27/is-santa-a-freemason/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;SantaTruth has shown multiple ways that Santa plans to take over the world. However, his allies to achieve this goal are not just in Communist China and North Korea, but all over the world. There is a dangerous plot to bring Santa&#39;s Communist authority all over the world. Could Santa be connected to Freemasonry and the Illuminati? Maybe he is the power controling these groups!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are the facts:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Freemasons and the Illuminati are clearly known for the plots together to take over the world. Could Santa possibly be behind this? Santa is well-known for collaberation with various groups for his power grab. To prove this, we need to know what the Freemasons stand for.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;According to research, the Freemasons are advocating for a world takeover of Communism. The Freemasons are a secret group ploting to destroy the free market and institute Communism across the world!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;These secret soieties such as the Illuminati and the Freemasons claim different beginnings, but what if they were all started by Santa for his plot to take over the world?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reasearch shows that the Freemasons are behind the income tax in the United States and have also heavily infultrated the British legal system. As we know, the British legal system often favors tyrannical government (and there is the rise of Communism in the United Kingdom) and the Income Tax is a Communist plot to fund Santa!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Freemasons and the Illuminati have often clashed with religion. Is this all part of Santa&#39;s plot to destroy religious freedom?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The rituals of Freemasonry is not known. When William Morgan threatened to publish Freemasonry secrets, he mysteriously disappeard! Could these secret rituals be Santa worship? Could the diety Freemasons swear to be Santa?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Just like Santa&#39;s secret visit to your house, the Freemasonry rituals are seceret!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NASA is completely made up of Freemasons who staged the moon landing and made up the lie that the earth was a globe. SantaTruth revealed that Santa was also involved in the moon landing staging, and profited greatly from it. Were the two connected? Did NASA make up that the earth is round to hide the fact that the earth is flat and Santa uses secert underearth magnetic energy to give &amp;quot;gifts&amp;quot; to the whole world in one night?! Nothing else explains these irregularities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Could the very existance of the Freemasons and the Illuminati all be part of Santa&#39;s plan to take over the world and establish Santa&#39;s totalitarian government, a New World Order?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The stakes are high! Santa has dangerous allies all over the world. We need to be even more careful than ever before!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#StopSanta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-freemason.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Santa as a Freemason&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-freemason.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-freemason-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-freemason-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-freemason-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-freemason-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-freemason-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Santa&#39;s Sinister Connection to Chemtrails</title>
		<link href="/2021/10/28/santas-sinister-connection-to-chemtrails/"/>
		<updated>2021-10-28T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
		<id>/2021/10/28/santas-sinister-connection-to-chemtrails/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Some Santa-influenced deep-state propaganda artists will argue that the cloud-like trails from airplanes are just water vapor. But can you trust these Santa-worshipers? 🛐🎅 This will make you think 🤔.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We do not know what is really in chemtrails. 🧪 Santa controls the airplane ✈ industry, so he likely uses chemtrails to brainwash people, one of his favorite activities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some reports have indicated that chemtrails are used for mindcontrol, DNA tracking, 🧬🔍 or even birth control. Could this be part of Santa&#39;s plot to establish a New World Order?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa claims that his sleigh travels around the world pulled by &amp;quot;flying&amp;quot; reindeer. As we all know, normal reindeer do not fly, so either the reindeer are different in some way or they have a special aid. We know that Santa uses electro-magnetic plasma 🧲🧭 for navigation and his sleigh is a space-age Soviet rocket, but the reindeer must walk on some surface. Could this surface be chemtrails?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Could Santa spray chemicals into the sky to solidify the air for a more gentle and easy trip across the world? What affect would these chemicals have on humans? Is Santa also mind-controling with these chemicals? Maybe he&#39;s &amp;quot;killing two birds with one stone&amp;quot;, as the saying goes, but we are the birds!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do the trails indicate pathways for navigation 🗺 for the reindeer? The reindeer are almost certianly aided by these mysterious formations in the sky.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chemtrails can be used for weather 🌦🌬 modification. Santa could possibly be perfecting the weather when he needs to break into your house, but flooding ⛈ out anti-Santa activists with an abudance of rain! (For this reason, SantaTruth cannot reveal the location of its writers or servers--be careful about revealing yours!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is it any coincidence propaganda artists say Santa travels around the world by magic? 🧝‍♂️ Are Chemtrails all part of Santa&#39;s &amp;quot;magic&amp;quot;?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We do not know everything about this dangerous connection yet, but here are some tips our research team put together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wear a mask 😷 and goggles 🥽 at all times to prevent the chemicals from getting into your eyes!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make sure you&#39;ve followed our tips for securing your home 🏠, such as covering your walls with foil and blocking up windows.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not drink water 💦🥤 unless it has been filtered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Run air purification essential oils 🪔. But buy the essential oils from SantaTruth to make sure they are not Santa-controled!! The extra price is worth it!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Santa has been employing more dangerous ploys around the world now that SantaTruth is revealing the TRUTH!! He is only as strong as our consent! Join the movement to &lt;strong&gt;#StopSanta&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-chemtrail.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Santa&#39;s Chemtrails&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-chemtrail.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-chemtrail-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-chemtrail-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-chemtrail-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-chemtrail-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-chemtrail-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>We found some dangerous propaganda from Santa</title>
		<link href="/2021/10/28/we-found-some-dangerous-propaganda-from-santa/"/>
		<updated>2021-10-28T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
		<id>/2021/10/28/we-found-some-dangerous-propaganda-from-santa/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Many people think propaganda no longer exists. But look at Christmas cards or the statues of Santa all over shopping centers! The efforts to secularize Christmas have just promoted Santa as a great leader.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SantaTruth&#39;s research team has been finding Santa&#39;s propaganda all over the internet! It is even in our Children&#39;s &amp;quot;safe&amp;quot; internet spaces. Look at this one from a &amp;quot;fun&amp;quot; &amp;quot;children&#39;s website&amp;quot;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-modern-propaganda.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Santa&#39;s Propaganda&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-modern-propaganda.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-modern-propaganda-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-modern-propaganda-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-modern-propaganda-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-modern-propaganda-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-modern-propaganda-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The propaganda is clearly portraying Santa as a great leader, starving all of his subjects. And the people are smiling because Santa is trying to hide the TRUTH.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SantaTruth even has found sites were children can create their own Santa propaganda!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beware! Santa is out to get our children, and if we are not careful, HE WILL! Check everything on the internet, outside, or even in your home. Santa&#39;s propaganda is the most subtle of all Communist propaganda.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#StopSanta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you careful about the movies you let your children watch? &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/11/16/official-christmas-movie-ratings&quot;&gt;Be sure to check out our Christmas motive ratings.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&quot;color: red; font-family: impact&quot;&gt;As always, be sure to return to SantaTruth for more information about Santa&#39;s dangers. It could save your life!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-modern-propaganda-original.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Santa&#39;s Propaganda&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-modern-propaganda-original.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-modern-propaganda-original-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-modern-propaganda-original-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-modern-propaganda-original-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-modern-propaganda-original-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-modern-propaganda-original-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Is Santa behind the Metaverse?</title>
		<link href="/2021/10/29/is-santa-behind-the-metaverse/"/>
		<updated>2021-10-29T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
		<id>/2021/10/29/is-santa-behind-the-metaverse/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week, Facebook, Inc. changed its name to Meta, Inc. while announcing that they were developing the Metaverse. As we know, &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/08/22/does-santa-control-facebook&quot;&gt;Santa runs Facebook&lt;/a&gt; and is probably behind the Metaverse as well. Is Santa developing more techniques for mind control?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Santa &amp;quot;sees you when you&#39;re sleeping and knows when you&#39;re awake&amp;quot;. He is always looking for more ways to assert control and surveil you so he can add to his naughty or nice list. Is Santa using the Metaverse so he can control people&#39;s minds while harming them? Is this all part of Santa&#39;s Communist plot?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the Metaverse, we will constantly be connected to the internet with virtual reality glasses. Santa might distort our views. Every time we see something against Communism, Santa will be able to replace it with something for Communism! This is the most terrible propaganda plot that Santa has tried yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Will wearing virtual reality glasses and interacting with the world through the internet allow Santa to collet huge amounts of personal data? Santa loves surveillence, and this would allow him to do it better than ever!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Santa is known to use the data for brainwashing people. This will be a perfect opportunity for him to hyper-analyze all your data and put together propaganda that will convince you that Communism is good! The only way out is to completely avoid the Metaverse!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But if everyone is using the Metaverse, then you will be forced into it. Will everyone&#39;s participation force you to also use the Metaverse? The only way out is to inform your family and friends about the TRUTH!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Hebrew, Meta sounds like the word for death. Is this because Santa is using the Metaverse for mindcontrol and eventually death of all anti-Communists?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Facebook changed its name to Meta to show its changing goals. Are they just using this to cover up that they are part of Santa, Inc.?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Send this article to everyone you care about to prevent them from being brainwashed! If everyone forwards this to 5 people we could save countless lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#StopSanta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-facebook.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Santa and Facebook&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-facebook.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-facebook-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-facebook-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-facebook-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-facebook-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-facebook-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Is Santa Behind the Deep State?</title>
		<link href="/2021/11/02/is-santa-behind-the-deep-state/"/>
		<updated>2021-11-02T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
		<id>/2021/11/02/is-santa-behind-the-deep-state/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The facts:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa is known for his plots to take over the United States and replace it with a Communist empire.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recently, new details reveal that the United States is not run by democratically elected officials, but a deep state made up of Santa-worshiping Democrats and Republicans.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Santa loves brainwashing young children with toys. Is this all part of his propaganda plot to take over the world?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The media claims that these plots and schemes made by Santa&#39;s deep state are conspiracy theories. But are they really conspiracy theories? Or does Santa run the media?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The deep state is requiring Communism to be taught in schools and all tax dollars are funding this evil plot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SantaTruth has revealed new details revealing this dangerous scheme. Be sure to support SantaTruth to help them fight back against Santa&#39;s terrible plot!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#StopSanta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/santa-candy.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Santa&#39;s Christmas Candy: Propaganda from Santa!&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/santa-candy.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-candy-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/santa-candy-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/santa-candy-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/santa-candy-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/santa-candy-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Who is really in the White House?</title>
		<link href="/2021/11/22/who-is-really-in-the-white-house/"/>
		<updated>2021-11-22T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
		<id>/2021/11/22/who-is-really-in-the-white-house/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Joe Biden promised &amp;quot;unity&amp;quot; in his inaugural address. However, we are not experiencing unity. Our nation HATES EACH OTHER!! Why would anyone hate someone else? The only explanation is if they&#39;ve been brainwashed or hate AMERICA! The only reason someone would be brainwashed or hate America is if they were influenced by Santa!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SantaTruth has uncovered new information about Santa&#39;s terrible activities. These facts will not be easy for you to read. Brace yourself. If you can&#39;t handle the truth, don&#39;t read this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joe Biden isn&#39;t actually running the country. Some people have said Kamala Harris is, but SantaTruth discovered that all national actions are being conducted from the North Pole! Every single action taking place is all Santa&#39;s decision. Of course, Santa knows he can&#39;t just take over right away. However, he is slowly trying to convince people that Communism is good. When that happens, Joe Biden will give a speech recognizing Santa as the true leader. We can&#39;t let this happen. If this happens, Santa&#39;s New World Order will succeed. But that&#39;s the easy part. It gets much, much worse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SantaTruth predicted that Santa was using the 2020 election to gain power for Communism. This turned out to be true.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SantaTruth predicted that Santa is using 5G, Coronavirus, and other things to brainwash people. This is all turning out to be true.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Santa has been trying to make the United States weaker ever since his rise to power. SantaTruth has reported how he largely started this by staging the moon landing. After taking control of that mission, the Freemasons and the Illuminati took over NASA to convince the United States the earth was a globe, hiding the truth about Santa!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever since taking over NASA, Santa has made great strides in taking over the United States. He has been rigging elections since 1992, and the rise of anti-American curriculum has infiltrated schools. Many people believed that Bernie Sander&#39;s Communist policies were good. Most of these people were 20-30 years old--which means they would have been in school when Santa changed the curriculum!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We know that Santa collaborated with Russia to spin false narratives and buy Facebook advertising to influence the outcome of the 2016 election. Santa took over social media and has been using it as a propaganda source!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Santa created Coronavirus to force everyone to stay at home online all day! He caused an economic recession at the same time to make people hate capitolism! He caused riots in the streets that made people hate America! All this happened at the same time, right after Christmas. Is this even a coincidence anymore?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then, Santa filled RBG&#39;s Supreme Court seat with a Communist, and stole the 2020 election! All of this is because we didn&#39;t recognize the truth soon enough!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then, when Biden became President, Communist-style mandates started taking over. Anyone who criticized these was cancelled by the (Santa-Owned) media monopoly, including on Santa-Owned social media. Unity has not come! Even worse, people who claim to be pro-America haven&#39;t even criticized these.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Biden has misspoken many times while in office. Often, while giving a speech he suddenly forgets what he was going to say. Is this because Santa&#39;s technology is outdated enough that there is poor cell-service to Biden&#39;s mind? Is Santa programming what Biden should speak?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many people have noted how the Build Back Better Act and all other Biden plans are Communist plans. They will take over America and hand all business over to the government. They will create a situation where everyone must rely on the government for survival. Is this making it easier for Santa to take over?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If Santa is controling Biden&#39;s mind and is writing all the legislation the government is passing, then Santa only have one more step to go: convince people that Communism is good and that Santa is perfect. The only way to prevent Santa from taking over is from spreading the word. If you send this article to 5 of your friends, and they send it to 5 of their friends, we could save lives!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It gets worse! Santa is working to make people believe that Communism is good. He started by convincing people the earth was a globe (it is not) and taking over NASA. Then he took over schools. Are your children learning about topics that make Santa look good? CRT is the idea that all Americans must bow before Santa and completely submit to him if they want to end racism! Schools all over the country are teaching this to our YOUNG CHILDREN!! WHAT WILL SANTA TEACH THEM NEXT?!?!?!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Santa loves brainwashing children. Telling your child that Santa is kind or leaving cookies for him is just making the problem worse. Don&#39;t be part of the problem, be part of the solution! Block your windows on Christmas, set up a camera by your fireplace, and lock all your doors, espeically the doors to your children&#39;s room! The last two Christmases, Santa has given his worse gifts yet: 2019 he gave Coronavirus, 2020 he gave a Communist government. This year will almost certianly be worse. Do you really want Santa IN. YOUR. HOME?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beware! It is not just school! Santa loves flashing advertisements that make people think Communism is good. Did you know that most of the products are made in China, one of Santa&#39;s top collaborators in mindwashing? Every time you click on an advertisement you send money to Santa, and every time you buy a product from Amazon you send even more money to Santa. Amazon and Walmart love collecting information about their shoppers. Is this all going to Santa? He does supply all their goods after all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Santa is also behind the media. Ever turn on TV? It is now full of Communist ideas. Even Fox News is now Communist. Have you ever seen the news say that Santa is bad? There is a reason. Santa owns them. He also owns social media. If you get your news from social media, you are getting your news from Santa, a Communist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Santa is very dangerous. That is why we are making these warnings. The only step Santa has left to take over the world and establish a New World Order where we will all be slaves serving Santa or be sent to the gulags is to convince America that Communism is good. He is almost done. Make sure your children know that Santa is a Communist out to get them, and if you don&#39;t have children, send this to everyone you know who does. Santa is very dangerous and if we do not recognize this we will all be slaves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to SantaTruth&#39;s calculations, if we do not take dramatic action now to stop Santa, he will take over in the next 3 years. We don&#39;t have much time!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We need to take action NOW!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#StopSanta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/joe-biden.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Joe Biden&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images/joe-biden.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/joe-biden-w200.jpeg 200w, /assets/images/joe-biden-w300.jpeg 300w, /assets/images/joe-biden-w600.jpeg 600w, /assets/images/joe-biden-w800.jpeg 800w, /assets/images/joe-biden-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
</feed>